Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Other Unions/Guilds/Federations
  - Screen Extras Guild (SEG): Correspondence, 1975, 1982-1987 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - Sindicato de Actores de Peru, 1964 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - Sindicato de Trabajadores [Radio, Television] de la Republica Mexicana, 1969 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - Sindicato Prof. de Musico, Chile, 1964 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - Society of Motion Picture and Television Engineers: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - South African Actors' Equity Association: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 174, Folder 21)
  - South African Film and Television Union (SAFTU), 1990 (Box 174, Folder 22)
  - Svenska Artisters Och Musikers Intresseorganisation (SAMI), 1986 (Box 174, Folder 23)
  - Svenska Teaterforbundet and Swedish Actors Union, 1964 (Box 174, Folder 24)
  - Syndicat national Des Actores: Correspondence, 1951, 1962-1964 (Box 174, Folder 25)
  - Syndicat Francais des Artistes-interpretes (SFA), 1985, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 26)
  - Television Authority (TVA): ABC v. TVA Brief of Petitioner, undated (Box 174, Folder 27)
  - Television Authority (TVA): Chorus Equity Association Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 174, Folder 28)
  - Television Authority (TVA): Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 174, Folder 29)
  - Television Authority (TVA): Correspondence, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 30)
  - Theatrical Mutual Association, 1958 (Box 174, Folder 31)
  - Unions: General, Non-performing Acts, 1963-1968 (Box 174, Folder 32)
  - United Scenic Artists: Correspondence, 1955, 1960, 1967 (Box 174, Folder 33)
  - Variety Artists Federation (London, UK): Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 174, Folder 34)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Agreement, 1960 Television Film Basic, 1960-1961 (Box 174, Folder 35)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA) [East]: Agreement, National for 1984-1987 (Box 174, Folder 36)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Agreement, WGA-AFTRA-Metromedia, Inc. Newsmen for 1961-1964, 1961-1963 (Box 174, Folder 37)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Agreement, WGA-AFTRA-Metromedia, Inc. Newsmen for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 174, Folder 38)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Agreement, WGA-Network Documentary Television Film Freelance Minimum Basic, 1960 (Box 174, Folder 39)
  - [Writers Guild of America (WGA)] Authors League of America Correspondence 1952 Television Agreement, 1951-1953 (Box 174, Folder 40)
  - [Writers Guild of America (WGA)] Radio Writers' Guild Agreement and Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 174, Folder 41)
  - [Writers Guild of America (WGA)] Radio Writers' Guild Correspondence and Related Materials, 1950-1952 (Box 174, Folder 42)
  - [Writers Guild of America (WGA)] Television Writers of America: Correspondence and Arbitration, 1953 - Jul 1954 (Box 174, Folder 43)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA) [as of Oct, 1954]: Correspondence and Related Materials, Oct 1954 - 1958 (Box 174, Folder 44)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1960-1963 (Box 174, Folder 45)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 174, Folder 46)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 174, Folder 47)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA) [East]: Persian Trust Fund Memo, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 48)
  - Writers Guild of America (WGA): Press Clippings, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 49)
- Series X: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; 12 websites in 12 archived websites.
  The American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), founded in 1937, is a national labor union representing performers, journalists and other artists working in the entertainment and news media. AFTRA's scope of representation covers broadcast, public and cable television, radio, sound recordings, "non-broadcast" and industrial material, as well as Internet and digital programming. In 2012, AFTRA merged with the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) to form SAG-AFTRA. The archived website for SAG-AFTRA contain information on the merger in 2012 of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). http://www.aftra.com/ became defunct in 2016. During the merger, the website contained news related to the merger, events, frequently asked questions, and a page on merger materials. Historically, the website contains news about the union, contracts, member benefits, press releases, information on locals, and other publications. The SAG-AFTRA website contains information on the organizing, member services, local unions, resources and relations with the entertainment industry, the SAG Awards, contracts, diversity campaigns, action campaigns, committees, news and other events. The series also contains the website for SAG-AFTRA Foundation, which provides educational programs, screenings, and resources to union members. SAG-AFTRA TV is the Youtube channel for the union. Videos include interviews, industry panel discussions on parenting, disability, background work, indigenous performers, sustainability, women performers, Black performers, senior performers, Middle Eastern and North African performer, LGBTQ performers; Latino performers, Asian and Pacific Islander performers, initmacy coordinators, technology; MOVE panels; celebrity events; actor to actor interviews; SAG Awards red carpet footage; award show behind-the-scenes footage; convention and summit highlights; union initiatives; COVID-19 updates; podcasts; contract overviews; business basics; and other videos. The SAG-AFTRA Young Performers website presents an overview of how to navigate the television and film industry as a young performing. It includes an FAQ; a glossary; information on child labor laws; interviews with Fred Savage and Candace Cameron Bure; videos from the SAG Awards and a mock negotiations workshop; a quiz on the Young Performers Handbook; and a PDF of the handbook. An additional microsite focuses on supporting SAG-AFTRA members with reporting sexual harassment in the entertainment and media industry, as well as a frequently asked questions microsite for SAG-AFTRA members regarding becoming a signatory, processing claims, the SAG awards, vaccination requirements, equity and inclusion, and the Music, Audiobook, Television, Commercial, New Media, Interactive, Influencer, and Theatrical departments.
  The American Scene Awards is a biannual award that honors union productions that employ the talents of people of color, people with disabilities, women, seniors, people who identify as lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, and/or queer and other misrepresented or under-represented groups resulting in the realistic portrayal of the American Scene. Three awards are bestowed: the American Scene Award in Entertainment, the American Scene Award in Music & Sound Recordings, and the Belva Davis American Scene Award in News & Broadcast. The website contains nomination information, FAQs, eligibility requirements, and a list of previous winners dating to 2013
  On July 13, 2023, SAG-AFTRA issued a strike after the Alliance of Motion Picture & Television Producers (AMPTP) failed to negotiate new TV/Theatrical agreements with the union. The website contains information about the strike notice; picket line conduct; picket calendar and locations; productions approved to interim agreements; FAQs for members and non-members, picketers, indie producers, talent representatives, influencers, personal appearances and conventions, podcasters, and broadcast; social media toolkit; strikebreaking reporting; and news.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  https://www.sagaftra.org/ is accrued quarterly. https://sagaftra.foundation/, https://www.youtube.com/user/SAGAFTRA/videos/, https://servicesagaftra.custhelp.com/app/sh/home/, and http://youngperformers.sagaftra.org/ are accrued semiannually. https://members.sagfoundation.org/programs/ is accrued monthly.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of sagaftra.org, servicesagaftra.custhelp.com, and sagaftra.foundation in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored.
  In 2023, YouTube URLs were changed to better capture the videos on the channel.